《致命女人》前情提要
Previously onWhy Women Kill...
他是个男人  有些男人是会出轨的
He's a man. Some of them cheat.
罗伯不会的  尤其是在失去了我们的女儿之后
Not Rob. Not after what happened to our daughter.
我爱上你了
I am in love with you.
你知道规则的  我永远不会离开我妻子
You knew the rules. I will never leave my wife.
要是他和她在一起那么幸福  为什么还要跟我在一起
Why would he even be with me if he was so happy with her?
或许她做了什么伤害他的事
Maybe she did something to hurt him
他需要时间去原谅她
and he needs time to forgive her.
我让我的炮友住进了我们家
I moved my lover into our home.
我们三个正式在一起了
The three of us are officially a throuple.
如果我明早不能把剧本给他
My agent's gonna drop me
我的经纪人就要炒了我
if I don't get him my script by tomorrow morning.
-把那50页给我  -直接说哪里不好吧
- Give me the 50 pages. - Skip to what sucks.
就是你的主人公
That would be your lead character.
-伊娃怎么了  -她差不多等了15页的篇幅
- What's wrong with Eva? - She waits around for 15 pages
就希望男人来拯救她
hoping a man will save her.
她是个受害者  我讨厌受害者
She's a victim. I hate victims.
话说你是怎么想到这种设定的呢
Hey, how did you come up with that stuff anyway?
或许我也并不像表面看起来这样
Maybe there's more to me than meets the eye.
那家伙可是个瘾君子
The man's a drug addict.
你们一半的积蓄都被他拿去买毒品了
Half your savings went up his nose.
Eli has changed.
等等  我有东西能帮你
Hold on, I have something.
吃掉它
Take this.
万一他比你更喜欢她了呢
What happens when he likes her more than you?
他说这是我写过的最好的剧本
He said it's the best thing I've ever written.
天  我真为你高兴
God, I am so happy for you.
你是在搞婚外情吗
Are you having an affair?
卡尔  我看你是嫉妒了吧
Karl, I believe you're jealous.
快告诉我这人是谁
Tell me who it is.
是我们乡村俱乐部的朋友吗
Is it one of our friends from the country club?
汤米回来了
Tommy's back.
还真是巧啊  亲爱的
Wasn't that lucky, dear.
汤米刚好在卧室
Seems Tommy was right there in the bedroom,
正派上用场
ready to be useful.
你不明白吗  我们不需要离婚
Don't you see? We don't need to get a divorce.
我们无意中卷入了这完美的安排
We have stumbled into the perfect arrangement.
不是什么都是笑话的  卡尔
Everything is not a joke, Karl.
我想要一个深爱我的男人
I want a man who loves me so much,
如果我和别人睡了  他会愿意去杀了那男人
that he would kill another man if I slept with someone else.
但是你永远做不到  对吗
And I'm never gonna get that from you, am I?
是的
No.
致命女人
第一季 第六集
目击者
萨蒙妮和我曾经关系很亲密
Simone and I used to be very close,
在我还是她理发师的时候
back when I was her hairdresser.
泰勒和我不得不交际
Taylor and I were forced to socialize,
因为我是她老公的经纪人
'cause I was her husband's agent.
我完全不了解贝丝·安  尽管她是我邻居
I didn't know Beth Ann at all, even though she was a neighbor.
我以前和她有聊不完的八卦
I used to gossip with her for hours.
她可喜欢我了
She adored me.
我试图在派对上和她聊天
I tried to talk to her at parties.
她从来听不懂我的笑话
She never got my jokes.
我以前会在集市上观察她
I used to watch her at the market.
她看上去人很好
She seemed nice.
人是种有趣的生物
It's funny about people.
他们每天都会进入我们的生活
They come into our lives every day...
你却永远不知道谁会扮演最重要的角色
...and you never know who will play the most important part.
一个完全的陌生人可能会救你于水火之中
A total stranger might be the one to save you
也可能将你推入深渊
or destroy you.
老实说
To be honest...
我感觉他的死我有责任
I feel responsible for his death.
要不是因为我  我不确定会有人死
I'm not sure anyone would've died if it wasn't for me.
我早知道她会杀了他
I knew she was going to kill him.
我也很高兴她这么做了
And I am so glad she did.
萨蒙妮
Oh, Simone.
-你怎么来了  -这算哪门子愚蠢的问题
- What are you doing here? - What a silly question.
你知道我有多喜欢我们的画廊
You know how much I adore our little gallery.
得了吧  你好几个月都没来过了
Oh, please. You haven't stopped by in months.
一旦我们开始谈判离婚协议
Once we begin negotiating our settlement,
我知道你会争取这个地方
I know you'll fight for this place.
你会告诉法官应该归你  因为我从没帮过忙
You'll tell the judge it should go to you because I never helped out.
我这就来帮忙了
Well, here I am helping out.
-打扰下  -你好  有什么事
- Excuse me. - Yes? Hello.
你们这有利希滕斯坦的作品吗
Do you have any Lichtenstein prints?
我们在谈话  能回避下吗
We're talking. Do you mind?
销售员工这么有魅力
And with charm like that on our sales staff,
我们的画定会卖得很快
these paintings should just fly off the walls.
今天不见汤米吗
No Tommy today?
我们今早谈过了
We spoke this morning.
是吗  是在电话里谈的
Oh, yes? Was that on the phone
还是在床上翻身敲他肩膀
or did you roll over and tap him on the shoulder?
我建议我们暂时别再见面
I suggested we take a break.
我的离婚律师认为和青少年搞婚外情
My divorce lawyer feels an ongoing affair
可能会让我显得没有同情心
with a teenager could make me seem unsympathetic.
你聘请了律师
You've hired a lawyer?
伯尼·莫顿  我前两次离婚就是他受理的
Bernie Morton. He did my first two divorces,
所以他知道我的喜好
so he knows what I like.
不不  我们说好要在艾米婚礼后
No, no, no. We-we agreed we weren't gonna get divorced
才离婚的
until after Amy's wedding.
我们说的是在那之前不对外宣布
We agreed not to announce it till then.
不代表我们不能先办手续
That doesn't mean we can't get the ball rolling.
可接下来几周我们会有很多事
B-But there's so much coming at us in the next few weeks.
艾米的俄克拉荷马亲戚明天会全体赶到
I mean, Amy's Oklahoma in-laws are turning up tomorrow en masse.
天哪  我怕极了那顿晚餐
Oh, God. I'm dreading that dinner.
我和布拉德的母亲就通了两分钟电话
I spoke to Brad's mother for two minutes on the phone.
-已经受不了她  -没错
- I already can't stand her. - Exactly.
如果我们还吵架
If we're fighting each other,
怎么有精力去讨厌他们呢
how will we have the energy to properly hate them?
你让我经历的那些事
After what you've put me through,
我的怒火多着是呢
I have more than enough rage to go around.
好吧  显然我们需要婚姻咨询
All right. Clearly, we need counseling.
能至少等到我们见过婚姻咨询师后吗
I mean, can we at least wait until after we've seen a therapist?
结束了  不再等了
It's over. No more waiting.
接受吧
Accept it.
好了
Well.
我想今天帮得够多了  回家见
I guess I've helped enough for one day. See you at home.
你看到泰勒的短信了吗
Did you see Taylor's text?
没有  我一直在写作
Uh, no. I've been writing.
她坐了早些的飞机
She got on an early flight.
一会儿就到家
She's gonna be here in a couple minutes.
-好  -我在想
- Oh, okay. - So, um, I was wondering,
你要什么时候告诉她
when you want to tell her?
告诉她什么
Tell her...?
关于昨晚
About last night?
咱俩做爱的事
And how-how we fucked?
你想提这茬
You-you want to mention that.
毕竟发生了  我们得坦诚相对  对吗
Well, it happened, so we have to be honest about it, right?
嗯  当然
Sure. Yeah.
-很好  棒极了  -嗯
- Great. Awesome. - Yeah.
但我在想  你觉得
I do wonder, though, um, what-what do you think
我们告诉她后她会怎样
Taylor's reaction will be when we tell her?
我觉得她不会介意
I-I think she'll be cool with it.
我们是三人行关系  她也见过我们做爱
I mean, we're in a throuple, she's seen us have sex before.
没什么大不了
I-It's-- it won't be a big deal.
有意思  很有意思
Mm. Interesting. That's interesting.
怎么了
What?
你觉得她可能会嫉妒吗
You think, you think she might get jealous?
也许  也许会嫉妒  也许会暴怒
Maybe. Maybe jealous, maybe furious.
很可能暴怒
I mean, likely furious.
是的  但你不觉得如果我们不说
Yeah, but don't you think she'll be angrier if we don't tell her
她自己发现后会更生气吗
and then she finds out anyway?
你看  这就是非常流行的
It-- well, see? See, that's where the ever-popular
"带进坟墓"哲学派上用场的时候
"Take it to our graves" philosophy would come into play.
你想保密
You want to keep it a secret?
老实说  这不是我的首选
I'll be honest, it's not my first inclination,
-但听你这么一说  我喜欢  -伊莱
- but hearing you say it out loud, I like it. - Eli.
不  我
No. I...
我们不能这样  感觉不对
We can't. That-that feels wrong.
那不对
That's wrong.
好吧  好吧  好吧
All right, all right, all right.
你说得对  你说得对
You're right. You're right.
非坦诚相待即背叛
Anything less than full honesty is a betrayal.
好吧
Okay.
她来了
Here she is.
-让我骄傲  -见鬼
- Make me proud. - Shit.
-嗨  -宝贝  旅途怎样
- Hi. - Hey, babe. How was the flight?
哭闹的小孩  婊气冲天的空乘
Crying babies, bitchy flight attendants,
弄丢了我的行李箱  还有我讨厌优步
they lost my suitcase and I hate Uber!
你们都干了什么
What have you guys been up to?
没什么
Uh... nothing much.
嗯  没错
Yeah. Yeah.
只是见你回家很开心
Just happy to have this one home.
不如给你泡个澡吧
What do you say we put you in a bath, huh?
-太好了  -你值得拥有  放浴盐吗
- Oh, my God. - You deserve it. Salt, no salt?
-多放点  -给你放满
- So much salt. - Salt it up.
你干什么呢
Whatcha doing?
我正想该把祖母的亚麻布
I was just trying to think of a place
都存放在哪里
to store all of Nana's linens.
如果世界爆发餐垫短缺危机
If there's ever a worldwide doily shortage,
我们绝对高枕无忧
we'll be sitting pretty.
大功告成
It is done.
正式全部开箱完毕
We are now officially unpacked.
我以为你几周前就完成了
I thought you finished weeks ago.
你说不喜欢看到箱子放的到处都是
You said you hated seeing all of the unpacked boxes lying around,
所以我就把它们放进了阁楼
so I put them all in the attic.
每天拿一个下来开箱整理
Every day, I would bring one down and empty it.
你把所有箱子都搬进了阁楼
You lugged all these boxes to the attic?
就为了让我眼不见心不烦
Just so I wouldn't have to look at 'em?
这没什么
It was nothing.
你每天做那么多事取悦我
You do so many things each day to please me.
我都没注意到的事
Things I don't even notice.
我想注意到  好谢谢你
And I want to notice them, so I can thank you.
我不想要感谢
I don't need to be thanked.
知道吗
You know,
过去几个月我经常加班
I've been working a lot of late nights the past few months.
我在忙的那个项目  快完成了
This project I've been involved with, it's almost over.
-是吗  -对
- It is? - Yeah.
一旦完成后
Once I'm done,
我们就能回到正常时间表
we'll get back to a normal schedule.
我会晚上准时回来吃饭  每晚都是
I'll be home in time for dinner, every night.
那我会非常开心
That would make me very happy.
我们终于搬进来了
So, we're finally moved in.
该怎么庆祝呢
How should we celebrate?
不如办个派对吧
Why not throw a party?
乔迁派对吗
Like a housewarming thing?
对  我们可以把邻居都请来
Yes, we can invite all the neighbors.
还有很多我没见过面呢
There's so many I haven't met yet.
那我们下周六办吧
Oh. Let's do it next Saturday.
-太好了  -很好
- That would be wonderful.- Fantastic.
-要我帮你把这箱子扔了吗  -先别扔
- You want me to throw this box away for you? - Oh, not just yet.
里面还有些照片
There's still some photos in there.
我本来想把这些摆到楼上的橱柜里
I was going to put those in the cupboard upstairs.
或许这一张该摆在外面
Maybe we should leave this one out.
真的吗
Really?
你说过这张让你难过
You said it upset you.
那是以前的事了
Eh, that was a while ago.
想起来让人很心痛
It hurts to remember,
但忘记更糟
but it'd be worse to forget.
你说得太对了
You're absolutely right.
萨蒙妮  我们要迟到了
Simone, we're going to be late.
来了  着什么急
I'm coming. Hold your horses.
艾米
Amy.
你和我们一起去吃晚饭吗
Are you coming with us to the dinner?
我们以为你会跟布拉德一家去
We assumed you'd be going with Brad and his family.
我整天都跟他们在一起  我需要喘口气
I was with them all day. I need a break.
他们真有那么难相处吗
Oh, are they really that bad?
你了解拖拉机吗
Do you know much about tractors?
不了解
Um, no.
-到上甜点时你就了解了  -你应该喝一杯
- You will by dessert.- I think you deserve a drink.
你这么努力
I'm sure Brad is very pleased
布拉德一定很高兴
that you're making such an effort.
相信我  我马屁拍到飞起
Trust me, I'm sucking up like crazy.
如果我能留下好印象
And if I make a good impression,
他父母可能会给我们买栋房子
his parents might buy us a house.
房子啊
A house?
作为结婚礼物吗
As a wedding gift?
亲爱的  我们送区区芝士火锅叉子可能不够
Darling, we really need to rethink those fondue forks.
他们的农场下面埋有大量石油
Their farm sits on millions of gallons of oil.
所以不管你对他们有什么看法  都友好一点
So whatever you think of them, be nice.
-我一向很友好  -要真心的
- I'm always nice.- Really nice.
不是皮笑肉不笑这种
Not bitchy nice.
你"绑住我手脚"了  不过行吧
You're tying my hands, but fine.
别接
Don't pick up.
-我们迟到了  -别担心
- We're late. - Uh, don't worry,
我们装了那种新型的机器
we've got one of those newfangled machines
能留言
that takes a message.
真不知道以前没有它时我们是怎么过的
You know, I don't know how we lived without it.
萨蒙妮  我是伯尼·莫顿
Simone, Bernie Morton here.
我在填写你的离婚文件
I'm working on your divorce paperwork,
但我还需要一些财务表格
but I still need some financial forms, so...
伯尼  现在不是时候
Bernie, it's not a good time.
我们明天再谈
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
你又要离婚吗
You're getting divorced again?
艾米
Now, Amy...
就在我婚礼之前
Right before my wedding?
不会影响你的
It won't affect you.
布拉德的父母如果认为养大我的女人
Brad's parents are not going to buy me a house
她的婚姻比薄荷糖的效力还短
if they think I was raised by a woman
是绝对不会买房子送我的
who's never had a marriage last longer than a breath mint.
你还怪我
You're blaming me?
是的  因为你换了三个老公
After three husbands, yes.
你这次又有什么借口
What's your excuse this time?
这个故事很有意思
It's a charming story.
没错  我俩都有有意思的故事
Y-Yes, well, we-we both have charming stories,
但我不想说一堆
but I don't want to bore you
我们英国人所谓的"荒唐事"  让你无聊
with a lot of what we Brits call, um, tommyrot.
行吧
Fine.
我们走吧
Let's just go.
荒唐事  你不是吧  卡尔
Tommyrot? Really, Karl?
你真可笑
You're hilarious.
我们终于意见一致了
At last, we agree on something.
早上好  我是贝丝·安·斯坦顿
Good morning. I'm Beth Ann Stanton,
你的新邻居
your new neighbor.
我和我丈夫刚搬到附近
My husband and I just moved in down the street.
我知道你是谁
I-I know who you are.
我听说你叫玛丽
Well, I hear your name is Mary.
玛丽·弗拉辛
Mary Vlasin.
终于见面了  真好
It's nice to officially meet you.
玛丽
Mary!
那是你丈夫吗
That your husband?
是的  现在不太方便
Uh, yes. Now's not a good time.
我很快就好
I'll be quick.
我有东西给你们
I have something for the two of you.
我就是为此而来的
It's the reason I dropped by.
是张邀请函
It's an invitation.
我和罗伯周六要办乔迁派对
Rob and I are throwing a housewarming party on Saturday;
没多隆重  就是小吃和啤酒
nothing fancy. Just finger food and beer.
邀请了一些老朋友来
We'll be having some old friends, and
希望也有新朋友来
hopefully some new ones.
我都不记得上次参加派对是什么时候了
I can't remember the last time I went to a party.
玛丽
Mary!
你觉得你们能来吗
Uh, do you think you might be able to make it?
我就想统计下人数
I'm just doing a head count.
我说不好
I don't know, um...
我本来要过去的  刚才在跟新邻居说话
I was coming. I was just, uh, talking to our new neighbor.
你好啊
Oh, hello there.
我不知道有人来了
I didn't realize we had company.
我是贝丝·安·斯坦顿
I'm Beth Ann Stanton.
刚搬到附近
I've just moved in down the street.
她邀请我们去参加  派对
She invited us to, uh, a party.
只是周六有个小小的乔迁派对
Oh.Just a little housewarming thing on Saturday.
玛丽说她不确定你们是否能
Mary said she wasn't sure you'd be able to...
哪有  我们很乐意参加
No, we'd love to come.
-是吗  -当然了
- Really? - Sure.
需要我们带点什么吗  或者
You want us to bring anything, or...
不用  不用
No. No.
你们两个小可爱来就够了
Just your lovely selves.
那好吧  到时见
Well, all righty, then. We'll see you soon.
太好了
Wonderful.
我去问问领班
I'll check with the maître d',
看看布拉德的家人是否到了
see if Brad's family's arrived.
我的天
Oh, my God.
-是赫克托  -赫克托
- It's Hector. - Hector?
他是我有过的最好的理发师
He was the best hairdresser I ever had.
我是说  直到他不干了
I mean, until he dropped me.
他为什么不干了
Why did he drop you?
谁知道呢  有一天他就突然停止了预约
Who knows? One day, he just stopped scheduling appointments.
你肯定做了什么冒犯他的事
Well, I'm sure you did something to offend him.
你为什么会这么想
Why would you assume that?
对哦  我很讨人厌
Oh, right, I'm horrible.
艾米
Amy!
佩蒂
Patty.
妈  这是布拉德的姐姐佩蒂
Mom, this is Brad's sister Patty.
很高兴认识你
Oh, it's lovely to meet you.
谢谢
Thank you.
他们把我们安排在私人包间里
Oh, they've seated us in a private dining room.
是你安排的吗
Did you arrange that?
是的  我想为我的新家人们做点什么特别的事
I did. I wanted to do something special for my new family.
真是个不错的主意
It's a great idea.
现在我们可以随心所欲大吵大闹了
Now we can get as loud and crazy as we want.
我不知道艾米是否告诉过你
I don't know if Amy told you,
我知道如何用约德尔唱法歌唱
but I know how to yodel.
以瑞士传统的真假嗓音交替歌唱
她没说过
No.
要是说过  我想我会记住的
I think I would have remembered that.
太好了  让我们开始狂欢吧
Great, let's get the party started.
-卡尔  大家都到了  -好
- Karl, everyone's here. - Oh, good.
-你好  -你好
- Hello. - Hi.
萨蒙妮
Simone.
大伙儿好
Hey, guys.
你们来啦
Oh, here they are.
认识你们甚是荣幸
What a pleasure it is to finally meet you.
我是露比  他是德怀特
I'm Ruby and this is Dwight.
-幸会  -你们好
- Charmed. - Well, hello, there.
抱歉我们迟到了
Sorry we're late.
如果你是忙着在打扮自己
Well, if you were busy making yourself beautiful,
请允许我说  任务完成了
may I just say, mission accomplished.
你真坏  德怀特
Heel, Dwight.
看来我得防着点你了
I see I'm gonna have to watch my step around you.
我无法告诉你们艾米能嫁给一个像你们儿子
I can't tell you how thrilled we are that Amy's marrying a young man
这么令人敬佩的年轻人我们有多激动
as admirable as your son.
听听这声线
That voice.
他就像是PBS电视台里的人
He's like someone on PBS.
谁想来点香槟
Now, who wants champagne?
大家都想吧
I'm sure we could all be persuaded.
我能听他说上一整天
I could just listen to him talk all day long.
如果你嫁给他  你会的
If you were married to him, you would.
露比和我也很喜欢你们的女儿
Well, Ruby and I are just as crazy about your daughter.
我们一家都是
The whole family is.
佩蒂不停地讲她
Patty hasn't shut up about her.
因为我很开心  好吗
'Cause I'm happy, okay?
我终于有个妹妹了
I'm finally getting a sister.
很激动我能成为大家庭中的一员
Well, I'm thrilled to finally be a part of a big family.
我总是梦想举办一场大型家庭聚会
I've always dreamed of hosting large family gatherings.
你们知道我的梦是什么吗
You know what I dream about?
抱孙子
Grandkids.
我也梦到过
Oh, I've had that dream.
每次都尖叫着醒来
I always wake up screaming.
你为什么不想抱孙子
Now, why don't you want grandkids?
那我就得告诉大家我当外婆了
Well, I'd have to tell people that I'm a grandmother.
看看我这面相  谁会相信我
And let's face it, who's gonna believe me?
还有人需要香槟吗
Does anyone need more champagne?
-天啊  需要  -需要  太需要了
Oh, God, yes. Yes, absolutely.
非常抱歉  我出去一下
Uh, I'm terribly sorry. Will you excuse me?
我非常需要去"飞流直下三千尺"
I, uh, I desperately need to use the facilities.
听听
Listen to him.
撒尿都说得这么花里胡哨
He even makes taking a piss sound fancy.
完成了  我刚写完
It is done! I just wrote the words
"消逝于黑暗中"
"Fade to black."
我的剧本完成了
My script is complete!
伊莱
Eli!
我的天哪
Oh, my God. Oh.
-宝贝  太棒了  -是的
- Honey, that's amazing. - Yeah, it is.
你知道最棒的是什么吗  不知怎的全都通了
You know what's amazing? Somehow it all works.
我是说  角色  情节  一切
I mean, the characters, the plot, all of it.
我可能用了"操"这个词
I mean, I probably used the word "Fuck"
六十多次  但是没关系
about 60 times too many, but that's fixable.
重点是我也许真的能成为一个好编剧
I mean, the point is: I may actually be a good writer.
我真为你骄傲
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
谢谢  谢谢
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
我给拉马尔打了电话
Oh, so I called Lamar,
然后他想请我们出去吃饭庆祝庆祝
and he wants to take us all out to dinner tonight to celebrate.
那太好了
Oh, that'd be great.
我们应该去月夜餐厅
We should go to La Serata.
-很好  -没错
- Ooh, molto bene. - Yeah.
我并不想换话题
Not to change the subject,
但有件事我很好奇
but I'm curious about something.
什么事
What's up?
我不在的时候  你们俩是不是睡了
While I was away, did you two fuck?
不知道为什么  我就是有这种感觉
I don't know why, I just have a feeling.
是我疯了吗
Am I crazy?
我们绝对睡了
We absolutely fucked.
天  真的啊  好吧
Shit. Wow. Hmm.
你生气了吗
Are you upset?
不好说
I'm not sure.
我俩又不是趁伊莱不在的时候没睡过
It's not like you and I have never done it without Eli.
那倒也是
That's true.
好吧
Okay.
Okay?
显然我还有些感受
I mean, obviously I have some feelings
需要平复
that I need to work through,
但这是...这是注定要发生的  对吧
but this was... this was bound to happen, right?
迟早的事  既然我们都住在一起了
At some point, since we're all together now.
而且我爱你们俩
And I love you both,
所以为何...我为何不想让你俩再走近点呢
so why... why would I not want you guys to get closer?
是啊  没错  我就知道如果我们能
Yes, exactly, and I-I knew that if we were just open
开诚布公地谈论整件事的话
and honest about the whole thing,
会发现其实也没什么大不了的
that it wouldn't be a big deal.
是啊  谢谢你告诉我真相
Yeah. Well, thank you for telling me the truth.
-知道真相后的感觉真不错  -那是当然了
- It feels good to know. - Of course. Of course.
对了  你应该告诉拉马尔
Oh, you know what, you should tell Lamar
发送给: 伊莱
你是个混蛋
我认识月夜餐厅的经理
that I know the manager at La Serata,
她能帮我们预定一个好位置
so she can get us a good table.
好啊  好啊
Oh, yeah, yeah.
行啊  行啊
Totally. Great call.
我会...
I will, um...
我立刻传简讯给拉马尔
I-I will, I will text Lamar right now.
好的
Okay.
伊莱:  我知道
我能感觉到罗伯还在生那晚的气
So I can tell Rob is still mad about the other night.
他已经多日没打给我了
He hasn't called in days.
我想过打给他
I thought about calling him,
但我不想让自己看起来太绝望
but I don't want to seem desperate,
虽说我确实有点绝望
although I am a little bit,
但他不需要知道这些
but he doesn't need to know that.
不管怎样...
Anyway...
你觉得我该怎么做
what do you think I should do?
你说什么
Hmm. What?
你看看我
Listen to me.
我一直叨唠罗伯  你一定听烦了吧
I must be boring you to tears always talking about Rob.
不  不好意思
No, I'm sorry.
我刚才在想今天遇到的这个女人
I was thinking about this woman I met today.
她在我脑海中挥之不去
I can't get her out of my mind.
为什么
Why?
我去她家送东西
I was at her door dropping something off,
感觉事情不太对
and, just, something wasn't quite right.
怎么说
How do you mean?
她很担心她丈夫
She was worried about her husband.
我能听到他喊她
I could hear him calling for her.
他的语气有些奇怪
There was just something about his tone.
着实吓到我了
It scared me.
然后他来开门
Then he came to the door,
看起来很有魅力
and he was charming.
这个女人  她是不是画着浓妆
This woman, was she wearing a lot of makeup?
确实是
She was.
你怎么知道的
How did you know that?
他经常打她
He hits her.
你觉得是这样吗
You think?
不  他不是那种人  他事业很成功
No, he isn't the type. He's very successful.
我父亲是名医生
My father was a doctor.
我过去常常看着我母亲用化妆品
I used to watch my mother apply makeup
来遮盖她青肿的眼眶
to cover up her black eyes.
不会吧
Oh, no.
她会先抹绿色的遮瑕膏来遮住淤青
She would smear green concealer to cover the bruise,
然后再涂一层遮瑕
and then she would apply a second layer of concealer
用以匹配她的肤色
that matched her skin tone.
然后她会在另一半脸上再重复同样的操作
And then she would do the same thing to the other side
这样人们就看不出来差别了
so that people wouldn't notice the difference.
那也太惨了
That's awful.
不  惨的在后面
No, here's the awful part.
我们全家都知道这件事
My whole family knew what was going on.
我的姑婶  叔伯  堂兄们
Aunts, uncles, cousins--
他们都清楚他做了些什么
they all knew what he was doing,
但是他们都视而不见
and they just looked the other way.
我恨那些视而不见的人
I hate people that look the other way.
他告诉店主无论吉布森兄弟开出什么价
And he told the owner he was willing to match
他都愿意出同样的价格
any offer the Gibson twins could come up with.
德怀特就是这样垄断了塔尔萨县
And that's how Dwight cornered the Tulsa County market
挖掘机市场的
for earth-moving machinery.
在那之后...
The next thing that happened...
请停下
Please stop!
等我找到卡尔再讲
Until I find Karl.
他一定不会想错过这个精彩的故事
He would hate to miss this amazing story.
他在洗手间待了好久了
He has been in the gents' room quite a while.
你想让我去看看他是怎么回事吗
Uh, you want me to check on him?
不用  我去就好
No. I-I've got this.
-女士  那是男厕  -我知道
- Ma'am, that's the men's room. - Oh, I know.
我丈夫总不会躲在女厕吧
My husband isn't hiding out in the ladies' room.
很开心我们终于见面了  拉马尔
So nice to finally meet you, Lamar.
我听了好多关于你的事
I've heard so much about you.
我也听说了很多你的事  美女
Heard a lot about you, too, pretty lady.
我有好多问题
And I have so many questions.
-求你别问  -拜托
- Please don't ask them. - Come on.
今天是我请客  我唯一想要的回报
I'm paying for this meal. All I want in exchange is
就是关于你们新生活方式的一些八卦
a few juicy details about your new lifestyle.
好吧  哥们  别让我难堪
All right, dude, don't embarrass me.
我要是没必要知道我就不会问了
I wouldn't ask if I didn't need to know.
你为什么需要知道
Why do you need to know?
事实是  我一直在考虑
Truth is, I've been thinking about
往我和德洛丽丝的关系中再添一个女人
bringing another woman into my relationship with Delores.
她不介意吗
And she's open to the idea?
当然介意
Absolutely not.
好吧  好吧
All right, okay, all right.
我们来谈谈我的剧本吧
Let's talk about my script.
-伊莱说你觉得不错  -不
- Eli said that you think it's good. - No.
我觉得棒极了
I think it's brilliant.
-告诉我能卖出去  -当然
- Okay, just tell me it'll sell. - Oh, yes.
已经有四个制片人感兴趣了
I already got four different producers interested.
我估计出价能有六位数  接近一百万
I'm expecting offers in the high six-figure range.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
我只会开性的玩笑  从不开钱的
I joke about sex, not money.
我以前的剧本从没有过这样的反应
I-I've never had a script get that kind of reaction before.
你从没写过这样商业的剧本
You've never written a script this commercial before.
我想我们得谢谢你
And I guess we have you to thank for that.
别
Stop.
什么
What?
只是
It just--
伊莱有点写不下去
Eli was having some problems with his story,
所以我看了前50页的剧本
so I read the first 50 pages,
给了他一些点子
and I-I gave him a few ideas.
不止一些  她可以说是救了我
More than a few. I mean, she saved my ass is what she did.
结尾那里  伊娃
That part at the end, where-where Eva,
她烧毁了那地方
she burns the place down and goes,
然后烧死了所有人
like, full-blown arsonist on everybody?
是洁德的点子
Jade's idea.
酷
Cool.
所以你剧本还没写完就拿给她看
So, you let her read the script before it was finished?
是的
W-Well, yeah.
你从没让我提前看过
'Cause you never let me do that.
不  亲爱的
No-- h-honey,
这次我实在是被逼入绝境了
my back was up against the wall on this.
-我  -我还
- I mean... - I-I also,
我给了他一些关于主角的想法
I-I gave him some thoughts on the lead character.
我很了解千禧一代的女生
You know, I have insight into the millennial female brain.
能看出来
And it shows.
伊娃是他笔下最棒的人物
Eva is the-the best character he's ever created.
这我可说不好
I-I don't know about that.
我可以  相信我  伊莱
I do. Trust me, Eli.
好好待洁德  她是你的灵感女神
Be good to Jade. She's your muse.
-你也许是对的  -别胡说了
- You might be right. - Oh, that's ridiculous.
洁德  你有想过自己写剧本吗
So, Jade, you ever think about doing any writing yourself?
有过  我
Um, yeah. I-I have,
我其实有几个剧本的点子
I actually have a couple script ideas, yeah.
我很有兴趣听听
Well, I would love to hear about them.
-真的吗  -嗯
- Really? - Yeah.
-失陪一下  -好
- Um, excuse me for just one moment. - Yeah.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
他总是在找我的替代者
He's always looking for my replacement, so please.
你到底是怎么想的
What in God's name?
该死  我们
Shit. We...
我们有点忘乎所以了
We got a bit carried away.
我们很久没见过面了
We haven't seen each other in years.
我的天  所以你才不给我理发了吗
Oh, my God. Is that why you dropped me as a client?
因为你在上我老公
Because you were screwing my husband!
我不能直视你的眼睛
I couldn't look you in the eye anymore.
没法给你剪刘海
It was impossible to trim your bangs.
我想你该走了
I think you should leave now.
不管有没有用
For what it's worth,
我喜欢你头发的层次感
I love the layers.
快滚
Go.
你怎么能这样
How could you?
你不至于这么吃惊吧
You can't be completely shocked.
你很清楚我和男人睡过
You knew perfectly well I slept with men.
可是和赫克托
But with Hector?
你惊讶于我睡的男人是你的理发师
You're surprised that the man I slept with was your hairdresser?
这就相当于同志性爱版的"是管家干的"
That is the gay sex equivalent of "The butler did it."
你们在干什么
What the hell is going on?
没什么  我们很好
Nothing. We're fine.
我们才不好
We are not fine.
你不会相信卡尔如何背叛了我
You would not believe how Karl betrayed me.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我拍了克莱皮特一家六个月的马屁
I've spent six months sucking up to the Clampetts,
我不允许你们一夜之间给我毁了
and you're not gonna blow it for me in one night.
赶紧出来
Now move it!
走吧
Come on.
我们就别破坏她卷进不必要抓马的机会了
Let's not ruin her chances with unnecessary drama.
行  我就等到我们上离婚法庭时再说
Fine. I'll wait till we're in divorce court.
我到时会做的事
And what I do to you then
就相当有必要了
will be very necessary.
格雷琴  戴尔  欢迎来到我们的聚会
Gretchen, Dale! Welcome to our little shindig.
-你好  -谢谢邀请我们
- Hi! - Thanks for having us.
天呐  你这短裤可真亮眼
Wow, those are some shorts.
是啊  专门为派对买的  很棒吧
Yeah. Bought 'em special for the party. Aren't they great?
饭厅里有食物和饮品
There's food and drink in the dining room.
-请自便  -谢谢
- Please help yourself. - Thank you.
-瞧吧  她喜欢我的短裤  -她可没这么说
- See? She liked them. - That's not what she said.
你好啊  贝丝·安  对曲目有什么要求吗
Hey, Beth Ann. Got any requests?
别弹古典曲目  除非等到我想赶客的时候
Don't play classical until I want people to leave.
好吧
Okay.
我是怎么跟你说的  不准在家里乱跑
What did I tell you? No running in the house.
但这不是我们家啊
But it's not our house.
我对天发誓  本尼
I swear to God, Benny.
拜托  经过古巴那事  没人会投票给他的
Come on. Nobody's gonna vote for the guy after what happened in Cuba.
那不重要  无论如何我都坚定认为
Don't matter. I can't think of one scenario
肯尼迪肯定会连任的
where Kennedy doesn't get a second term.
那是不可能的
Never gonna happen.
所以你从没乘过凯迪拉克吗
So you're telling me you've never been for a ride in a Cadillac?
我很乐意带你兜兜风
I'd be happy to take you around the block.
莉诺  你能来厨房给我帮帮忙吗
Lenore, could you please help me in the kitchen?
真是太感谢了
Thank you so much.
亲爱的  麦尔斯在吹嘘他在休斯飞机公司的薪水
Honey, Miles is bragging about his salary at Hughes Aircraft.
我能告诉他我的薪水吗
Can I tell him how much I make?
-绝对不要  -拜托
- Absolutely not. - Oh, come on.
饼干
Cookies!
那是魔鬼蛋吗
Are those deviled eggs?
请自便
Help yourself.
嗨  你们来了
Hi. You came.
当然了  我们不会错过的
Of course. We wouldn't miss it.
很抱歉我们迟到了
I'm sorry we're late.
别说傻话  派对才刚刚开始呢
Don't be silly. The party's only just started.
你这房子可真漂亮啊
Nice place you got here.
我们的确很喜欢
We certainly like it.
我不想空手而来  所以...
Well, I didn't want to come empty-handed, so...
你不必如此麻烦的
You shouldn't have.
不  不麻烦  我用的是现成的糕点粉
No, no. It was no trouble. I used a mix.
再次感谢你邀请我们
Thank you again for inviting us.
亲爱的  你看  那是戴尔·克拉克
Look, honey, it's Dale Clark.
我认识他  我们应该去打个招呼
I know him. We should go say hi.
瞧瞧他的短裤
Look at those shorts.
泰勒  你还在吗
Taylor? Are you still in here?
泰勒
Taylor?
你在这儿啊
There you are.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
男人们都开始担心了
The boys are starting to worry.
我没事
I'm fine.
-你确定吗  -是的
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
在方便呢  马上就出来
Doing my thing. I'll be out in a minute.
那你的裤子为什么没脱
Why are your pants on?
那你为什么这么奇怪
Why are you being weird?
抱歉
Sorry.
听着  如果你生气了  我完全理解
Look, I understand if you're upset.
是吗
Do you?
我和伊莱之间发生的事
What happened with me and Eli
显然触发了某些伤痛的感觉
has obviously triggered some hurt feelings,
我真的完全理解的
and I totally get it.
洁德  如果我说
Jade, believe me when I say
我完全不在乎你跟我丈夫上床的事  请你信我
I don't give a fuck if you screwed my husband.
好吧  那问题到底是什么
Okay, so then what's the problem?
他的灵感女神  那是什么狗屁话
His muse? What kind of over-the-top undeserved bullshit is that?
好吧  他只是想说些客气话而已
Okay, he was just trying to be nice.
你没有拯救他
You didn't save him.
你不过是抛出一些想法
You toss out a couple ideas
在他熬夜时  给他到咖啡而已
and poured him coffee while he pulled an all-nighter.
过去两年  他把我们的生活毁得千疮百孔
I am the one who spent the last two years
收拾烂摊子的人是我
cleaning up the mess he made of our lives.
-他干什么了  -他什么没干
- What did he do? - What didn't he do?
安非他命  可卡因
Speed, cocaine...
老天呐  我都能写个清单出来
Christ, I can write you a list,
但这地方半夜就打烊了
but this place closes at midnight.
洁德  他是个瘾君子
Jade, he's an addict.
他曾经差点死了
He almost died.
如果不是我强迫他戒毒  他已经死了
And he would've if I didn't force him into rehab.
我之前不知道这事
I-I didn't know that.
你怎么可能知道
Well, how could you?
我什么都没说  因为...
I didn't say anything because...
我以为我们已经没事了   但是...
I thought we were fine and...
你来了以后  就...
just having you here, it's...
什么
What?
老天  这暴露出了我们之间的感情的裂缝
Man, that's just shining a light on the cracks in our relationship.
-我不是有意...  -我知道
- I don't mean to... - I know.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
你没做错任何事  我只是...
You did nothing wrong. I'm just...
我也说不清
I don't know.
我只是不太确定
I'm just not sure
当前的共处形式是否可以成立
the current living situation is working.
你的意思是你希望我离开吗
Are you saying you want me to go?
我也不知道我是什么意思
I don't know what I'm saying.
我只是觉得  目前的这种关系是行不通的
I just don't think this whole thing's working.
希拉  希拉  快来
Sheila! Sheila! Come on.
你干什么
What're you doing?
你没听到吗  他们在弹奏《扭扭舞》呢
Don't you hear? They're playing "The Twist."
真是太棒了  我在吃派呢
That's terrific. I'm eating pie.
别吃什么派了
Forget about the pie.
-快来  我想跳舞  -你的舞伴在这儿呢
- Come on. I want to dance. - Well, here's your partner.
她就跟我一样  不过更小  更娇弱
She's just like me, but smaller and stickier.
来吧  亲爱的  等我们跳完舞
Come on, honey, and after we're done dancing,
爸爸要跟你讲讲那些
Daddy's gonna tell you about all the nice women
他本该娶的所有好女人
he should've married.
嗨  要来一起跳吗
Hi. Joining us?
我看看  抬起腿
Let's see it. Lift your leg.
-你还好吗  格雷琴  -我的高跟鞋跟断了
- You okay there, Gretchen? - I broke my heel.
我马上回来  阿斯泰尔先生
I'll be right back, Mr. Astaire.
你跳得太棒了
You're a killer.
她才是
Well, she is.
玛丽
Mary.
可以邀请你跳支舞吗
May I have this dance?
不  算了吧
No, I don't think so.
拜托  别让我独自跳舞啊
Aw, come on. Don't make me dance alone.
真的  我有两只左脚[不会跳舞]
Seriously, I have two left feet.
跟我的加一起我们就有四只脚了
Well, add them to mine and we'll have four.
-好吧  就跳一下  -这就对了
- Okay, just for a minute. - Yeah, now you're talking.
你跳得不错啊
Look at you go.
抬起手
Hands up!
我的错  你跳得很好
My mistake. Oh, you're doing great.
过来
Come on.
-我们只是在跳舞  -我说了过来
- We were only dancing. - I said come on!
伙计
Buddy.
没有必要这样
There's no need to be like this.
你可以随心所欲绿你妻子
You can cheat on your wife all you want,
但是休想碰我妻子
but you're not touching mine.
你看到了吗
Did you see that?
是的
Yeah.
他当着所有人的面把她抓走了
He just grabbed her and pulled her away in front of everyone.
他很生气她在跟我跳舞
He was angry that she was dancing with me.
这不是借口
That's no excuse.
他们进书房去了
They went into the study.
你得去确保他没有伤害她
You need to make sure he's not hurting her.
怎么
Well?
他们婚姻中的事情跟我们没有关系
What happens in their marriage is none of our business.
所以我们才去参加各种派对吗
Is that why we go to parties?
好让你能跟陌生男人调情吗
So you can flirt with strange men?
人们可以听到你
People can hear you.
或者是你就喜欢侮辱我
Or do you just enjoy humiliating me, huh?
能出去吗  这是私人对话
Do you mind? This is a private conversation.
如果我们太吵了  我向你道歉
Look, I am so sorry if-if we are being too loud.
我们很快就会离开  好吗
We'll be out of here in two shakes of a lamb's tail, okay?
听着  这不是我的错
Look, this is not my fault.
她总是喝太多
She always drinks too much.
我刚刚在饭厅里摆上了一份天使蛋糕
I've just set out some angel food cake in the dining room.
你们不去吃一块吗
Why don't you go have a slice?
不了  谢谢
No, thank you.
我们要回家
We're going home.
或许你想再多待一阵子
Maybe you'd like to stay a little longer?
给他个冷静的机会
Give him a chance to cool off.
这只会让事情变得更糟糕
That'll just make it worse.
玛丽
Mary.
能像你这样坚强
It must be a wonderful thing
一定很棒吧
to be strong like you.
所以我们才变成了美南浸信会教徒
That's the reason we became Southern Baptist.
循道宗教徒有点过于自由了  不合我们口味
Those Methodists were just a little too liberal for our taste.
酒瓶就别拿走了
Leave the bottle.
亲爱的  你不觉得
My darling, don't you, uh,
你喝得够多了吗
think you've had enough?
对你  我确实是受够了
Of you? Yes.
霞多丽吗  绝对不会
Of chardonnay? Never.
佩蒂
Patty!
看看你的新裙子
Look at your new dress.
该死
Oh, darn.
艾米帮我买了时髦的衣服
Amy helps me buy something chic
我第一次穿就把它弄脏了
and I ruin it first time out.
我们明天再去购物
We'll just go shopping again tomorrow.
你需要爽身粉来除掉丝绸上的油渍
For grease on silk, you want talcum powder.
租车里有个旅行装的
There's a travel size in the rental car.
好   失陪下
Okay. Excuse me.
布拉德跟我说你们俩一起开了艺术画廊
Brad tells us you two run an art gallery together.
感觉如何
What's that like?
-有趣  -很有挑战性
- Fun. - Challenging.
是很有挑战性  但也很有趣
It's a challenge, but a fun one.
不像我们的婚姻  完全就是挑战
Unlike our marriage, which is purely a challenge.
说起婚姻
Speaking of marriage,
我很好奇  萨蒙妮
I'm just curious, Simone,
你结了几次婚
how many times have you been married?
就三次  怎么了
Just three. Why?
只不过是个无关痛痒的问题而已  亲爱的
It's just an innocent question, my love.
-我没在跟你说话  -我知道
- I wasn't talking to you. - I know.
你为什么那么生他的气
Why are you so cross with him?
我没有生气  我有生气吗
I wasn't cross. Was I cross?
你绝对生气了
You were definitely cross.
当然了这不关我事  但是...
Um, not that it's any of my business, but...
如果我离过两次婚  能遇到卡尔这样的男人
if I were twice divorced, then hooked a man like Karl,
我会更加善待他的
I'd treat him a little nicer.
换到我好奇了  露比
Now I'm curious about something, Ruby.
如果你走进盥洗室里看到他跟男人接吻
How would you treat Karl if you walked into the bathroom
你会怎么对待他呢
and found him kissing another man?
真棒  萨蒙妮
Bravo, Simone.
没错  甜心
That's right, sugar.
卡尔是同性恋
Karl is gay.
还对他有感觉吗
Still have a crush on him?
你继父是同性恋
Your stepdad is gay?
我以为他的谈吐举止是因为他是英国人呢
I thought he was just English.
这就是我们离婚的原因
That's why we're getting divorced.
天哪  又要离婚
Dear God. Another divorce?
这不是重点  德怀特
Not really the headline, Dwight.
你这个可怜的女人啊
Oh, you poor, tragic woman.
我的确受过苦
I have suffered. It's true.
不好意思  别为西蒙娜难过了
I-I'm sorry, do not shed tears for Simone.
她从她的情人那里
She is receiving ample comfort in the arms
得到了足够的慰藉
of her lover
也就是汤米·哈特
Tommy Harte.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
闭嘴  卡尔
Shut up, Karl.
你跟汤米上床了
You're sleeping with Tommy?
你们可能不知道  他才刚刚18岁
Who, for the newcomers, is all of 18 years of age.
我的老天爷啊
Oh, sweet suffering Jesus.
英国同性恋  青少年情人
British homos, teen lovers?
这是要结什么鬼亲家
What kind of spangled hell pit are you marrying into?
我找到爽身粉了
Hey. Found the talcum powder.
为什么大家都这么严肃
Why is everyone so serious?
我从来没想到有一天我的家里
I never thought I'd see the day our family
会有一个同性恋
would have a homosexual in it.
布拉德  你发誓不会说出去的
Brad, you swore you wouldn't tell.
不  佩蒂  佩蒂  我...
No, Patty, Patty, I-I...
我不知道布拉德跟你说了什么
I-I don't know what Brad told you,
但是我对你的感情是姐妹情  不是姬情
but my feelings for you are sisterly, not sexual.
我的天老爷啊
Oh, sweet suffering Jesus.
佩蒂
Patty!
回来
Oh, come back!
亲爱的  这一定不是真的吧
Sweet baby, please say it's not true.
她是同性恋
She's a lesbian.
我怎么会没看出来
How did I miss that?
有人要来一杯餐后鸡尾酒吗
Anybody want an after-dinner cocktail?
我就不了  我现在头很疼
Uh, not me. I have the worst headache.
那你去楼上躺着吧
Why don't you go on upstairs and lie down?
我们今晚就不打扰你了
We can give you a little space tonight.
那太好了  谢谢
That'd be nice. Thank you.
我要来杯苏格兰威士忌  你要吗
I'm gonna have me a scotch. You want one?
洁德
Jade?
你为什么不告诉我
How could you not tell me?
我不知道你指的是什么...
I'm not sure I know what you're talking...
那些药  伊莱
The pills, Eli.
你有毒瘾还接受了我给你的药
You're an addict and you let me give you pills.
我去
Shit.
-你是怎么...  -泰勒告诉我的
- How did you... - Taylor told me.
晚餐的时候在卫生间告诉我的
At dinner, in the bathroom.
我去  她...
Shit. She d--
但她不知道我吃过什么吧
she doesn't know that I took anything, though, right?
不知道
No.
-谢天谢地  -还不知道罢了
- Oh, thank Christ. - Not yet.
不  不  不
No. No. No, no, no, no, no.
你这"不"是什么意思
What do you mean, "No"?
我必须告诉她  这是件大事
I have to. This is too big.
我去
Fuck.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
她已经开始质疑我们目前的生活状况
I mean, she's already questioning our living arrangement.
如果她发现了的话
If she finds out about this,
不管她还对我还有什么感觉  我肯定要被赶出去
it doesn't matter how she feels about me. I am out on the street.
我无处可去  伊莱
I don't have anywhere to go, Eli.
薇珞和米莎走了
And Willow and Mischa are gone
但杜克还在
and Duke is still out there.
听着  洁德  洁德  听我说
Listen. And I...Jade, Jade, listen-listen to me.
不会这样的  我不会让事情变成这样的
That's not gonna happen. Okay? I'm not gonna let that happen.
-我需要你在这里  -为什么
- I need you here. - Why?
我是你的灵感女神还是你的毒贩
Because I'm your muse or am I, am I just your dealer?
我已经戒掉了  好吗
I'm-I'm done with the pills. Okay?
戒了
Done.
她不需要知道
So she doesn't need to know.
如果是那样的话  那还给我
In that case, give them to me.
-什么  -如果你戒了的话
- What? - If you're done with them,
就没有理由不把它们还回来了吧
then there's no reason that you can't give them back.
所以呢
So?
但是现在感兴趣的制片人之一
Look, the thing is, one of the producers who's interested
-想要我改写  -我就知道
- wants a rewrite.- I knew it.
她有一些很棒的点子
She's got some really great ideas.
-拉马尔说如果我可以在周五之前交稿的话...  -伊莱
- Lamar says if I can turn out a draft by Friday...- Eli.
好的  好吧
All right, fine.
天哪  拿走吧...
Jesus, just take them....
我离事业东山再起
Just, I'm-I'm-I'm so, I'm so, so close
只有一步之遥了
to getting my career back.
没有这些东西你也可以改写成功的
You can handle a few rewrites without them.
是啊  我只知道我曾是个编剧
Yeah, all I know is that I used to be a writer
也是个瘾君子  然后我戒毒
and an addict, and then I got clean,
突然之间  我就不再是编剧了
and all of a sudden, I wasn't a writer anymore.
但如果我这次做到了
But if I can do this,
如果我可以  可以完成这个剧本
if I can, if I can finish this thing
如果我可以按时把作品交上去的话
and if I can get it to them on time,
那我就...
then, you know, I'm...
我就能回归
I'm back.
我就能再次走上巅峰
I will be legit again,
他们就会再次信任我
they will trust me again
然后就会有收入了  洁德...
and the money that will follow, Jade...
我就可以照顾你了
...I can take care of you.
求你了
Please.
我需要它们
I need them.
你保证你会照顾我吗
And you promise you'll take care of me?
我保证
I promise.
我们去忙你的剧本吧
Let's get to work on your movie.
天  今晚真是"惊喜不断"啊
Christ, what an evening.
我累死了
I'm exhausted.
你今晚不能待在这儿
Oh, you're not staying here tonight.
是吗
Is that so?
我要你立刻收拾东西离开
I want you to pack your things and leave, now.
少来了  萨蒙妮
Oh, knock it off, Simone.
我已经够生气了
I'm angry enough as it is.
你生气  我女儿也许再也不会跟我说话
You're angry? My daughter may never speak to me again.
那能怪谁呢
Oh, and whose fault is that?
你之前要是闭嘴而不是羞辱我就行了
If you'd just kept your mouth shut instead of humiliating me.
你把我激怒了
I was provoked.
所以无论如何你也不可能抑制住
Oh, so there was no possible way you could suppress the impulse
你想破坏今晚的冲动了
to blow up the entire evening?
你好意思说  你随时
Says the man who couldn't stop himself
都想溜进男厕所去快速打一炮
from sneaking off to the men's room for a quickie.
去你妈的
Oh, fuck you!
我一辈子都在控制自己
I've spent my whole damn life controlling myself,
隐瞒我的本质
hiding the central fact of my existence
就为了不让我家人  朋友或妻子失望
so I wouldn't disappoint my family, my friends or my wife.
只有赫克托
Hector was the only person
能看清我真实的为人
who ever saw me for the man I truly am,
而不是那个我假装的人
not the one I was pretending to be.
你根本不知道他对我的意义
You have no idea what he meant to me.
别再浪漫化你肮脏的一时放纵
Stop romanticizing your grubby little fling.
我爱过他
I loved him!
他叫我跟他私奔
He asked me to run away with him.
但我对你许下了承诺
Um, but I-I had made a commitment to you,
所以我选择留下
so I chose to stay.
我是你妻子
I am your wife.
你没离开我难道要感激你吗
Am I supposed to be grateful that you didn't walk out?
我只希望你能从我的角度来看这事  哪怕就一次
I just want you to see it from my perspective for once.
想想
Just think
我为了信守我对你的誓言而失去了什么
about what it may have cost me to honor the vow I made to you.
所以不  萨蒙妮  我不指望你
So no, Simone, I do not expect you
感激我所做出的牺牲
to be grateful for the sacrifice I made,
可是你好歹承认吧
but for fuck's sake, at least acknowledge it.
我要去睡了
I am going to bed.
不去客房睡
Not in the guest room.
我要去我们的房间  在我们的床上睡
In our room, in our bed.
你想在哪睡都行
You sleep where you like.
汤普森一家刚走
The Thompsons just left.
让我替他们谢谢你的热情招待
Said to thank you for a lovely time.
不跟我说话了
So, you're not talking to me.
我要说什么
What am I supposed to say?
那是个派对
It was a party.
我不会闹出什么幺蛾子的
I wasn't gonna cause a scene.
他伤害了她  就在你面前
He hurt her, right in front of you,
你却袖手旁观
and you did nothing.
我能做什么  打他吗
What was I supposed to do? Hit him?
我们的客人肯定会喜欢我那么做的
I mean, I'm sure our guests would have loved that.
你本可以跟他对峙的
You could have at least confronted him.
让他知道那种行为是不能接受的
Reminded him that kind of behavior is unacceptable.
他喝了酒
The guy had been drinking.
他肯定不是有意伤害她的
I-I'm sure he didn't mean to hurt her.
这不是他第一次对她动手了
This is not the first time he's gotten rough with her.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
她手臂上有好几处淤伤
She had several bruises on her arm.
所以她才在这么热的天里穿长袖
That's why she's wearing long sleeves on such a hot day.
如果有那么糟的话  她怎么不离开他
If it's that bad, why doesn't she leave him?
她能去哪  罗伯  这里吗
And where would she go, Rob? Here?
你愿意让她睡我们家沙发吗
Will you let her sleep on our sofa?
老天  贝丝·安  我不知道
Jesus, Beth Ann, I don't know.
万一拉尔夫在半夜
And what if Ralph comes banging on our door
来猛敲我们家门  想拖她回去呢
in the middle of the night to try to drag her back?
你会有种和他对抗吗
Would you have the balls to stand up to him then?
别用这种语言
Don't use that kind of language.
你当然不会了  你只会像个懦夫一样
Of course you wouldn't. You would just slink away
偷偷溜走
like the coward you are!
够了
Okay!
他不是完美丈夫
He's not the perfect husband.
轮不到我对他评头论足
It's not my job to judge him!
你想要邻居到我们家来
Would you like the neighbors coming in here
因为你不是完美母亲而对你评头论足吗
and judging you for not being the perfect mother?
我意思是  别管了
I'm just saying, leave it alone.
我不知道你还在这儿
I didn't know you were still here.
我刚在楼上
I was just upstairs.
收拾垃圾
Just... picking up some trash.
所以你都听到了
So you heard everything?
嗯
Yeah.
你们在吵什么
What was that all about?
亲爱的
Honey.
没事
It's okay.
你可以跟我说
You can talk to me.
不管是什么  我不会评判你
Whatever it is, I don't judge.
我们的女儿因我而死
Our daughter died because of me.
闯祸的是我
I'm the one who's responsible.
萨蒙妮
Simone.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
我得知道  你爱他吗
I need to know. Do you love him?
爱
I do.
那就邀请我进屋
Okay, then invite me in.
我们有很多要谈的
We have a lot to talk about.